



Ferring, BN12



07951235998



sisan@live.co.uk



alexsisan.co.uk

PROFILE & APPROACH

For the past six years, I have been designing digital products, gaining a solid foundation in the principles of visual design and interaction design. I'm a creative thinker who loves solving problems, challenging my creative boundaries, researching and designing products with the user experience at the heart of every project. I have been fortunate enough to work alongside pioneers in the industry, developing my theoretical understanding of user experience. I always embrace a challenge whether working as part of a team or individually.

EDUCATION

Bournemouth University 2013 - 2017

BA Hons Digital Media Design with placement year First Class Honours

As part of the degree, I was open to a wealth of theoretical and practical elements of design. In my final year I designed, developed and built an IOS app - Boozebible.

Brighton & Hove VI Form College 2009 - 2011

A Levels

Media Studies, Business, ICT & Psychology

St. Andrews High School 2005-2009

GCSE

10 A - C (Including Maths and English)

SKILLS

UX/UI design
Usability testing
Responsive web design
App design
User journey creation and optimisation
Concept and innovation generation
Wireframes and interactive prototypes
HTML & CSS
Sketch
Adobe Creative Suite

EXPERIENCE



Creative Intern

Clearleft, November 2017 - May 2018
As part of my Clearleft internship, I have had the ability to expand my theoretical understanding of user experience and put my skills into practice. I was a member of the team responsible for designing the customer experience for UX London & Leading Design. We covered all touchpoints, including marketing channels, website and the event itself. I played a significant role in conducting guerilla user testing for Greater London Authority as well as participating in Design Sprints for Virgin Atlantic, where the focus was to help Virgin Atlantic create a more Virgin-Like help centre.



Freelance Digital Product Designer

alexsisan.co.uk, June 2011 - to date
Since 2011 I have worked on a variety of
projects from visual design, brand development,
user research and web design for small
businesses with the user being the heart of
every project. Most recently, I was
commissioned to build a startup company's
brand from the bottom up- Ashley James Meat
Company. I worked closely with them to design
the logo, establish a brand identity and
prototype plus design & develop their website.
We also established a tone of voice for the
company's presence on social media.



Marketing Assistant (Design)

Lawrence Harvey, July 2015 - June 2016
As part of my degree, I did a year in industry. I was given the opportunity to solely own the design aspect with the supervision of the Group Marketing Manager. My main achievements were the design and development of two websites for the group's subsidiary companies (Harper Harrison & Piper Maddox) as well as the development of the Tom Glanfield's (CEO) personal website. I single handedly designed & developed these websites, with a focus on the target audience while taking into account the needs of the stakeholders.